{
    "id": "f3799fbc1e624a6697ba57b38d8f3ac5",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The doctor suggested ........................................ take a vacation.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the patient to",
                "that the patient should",
                "that the patient to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "28495d48e9bd4a38a50c3a8d438639c0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Learning ........................................... isn’t easy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "French",
                "the French"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e8653a82c73642f4839ac03a8b3451bc"
        },
        {
            "question": "I need .............................................. sleep.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "a good"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c05101df64b24bb18f12363c845e898f"
        },
        {
            "question": "We had ............................................. time on the top of the mountain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "great",
                "a great"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a5c708d928814ad6895893dcac9f6e51"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am going to the hospital to see a friend who has undergone .......................................... operation.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the",
                "an",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "75f7b3cdd12342dba96840e6d60c58a4"
        },
        {
            "question": "The more you read the ........................................... you understand.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d247aab1c0154407bb7ba1cf7e74618d"
        },
        {
            "question": "On the way home, I saw an old beggar accompanied ............................................ a child.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "33a4f81ba9754954a44f19f59767f816"
        },
        {
            "question": "Will you please .................................................. me a copy of ‘The Old Man and the Sea’?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lend",
                "borrow"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fab8a5c9deb1470692f12cf34b399a5c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The man who knocked ............................................. the door was a stranger.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "54bf8b0826ce466388bb7b620a06d2bf"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the difference .............................................. these cars?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "between",
                "among"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1d03e2a5d4b843abbfc8514766d69a5e"
        }
    ]
}